'Cause every time I see your face
당신 얼굴을 볼 때마다
당신 매력에 빠져들어요
I can't help but fall from grace
노래 좋다
This girl's good.
운율이 좋은 노래지
난 생각도 못한 건데
Yeah, a song with rhyming words!
I never thought of that before.
I like her.
맘에 들어
노래와 기타 때문에 좋아?
아님 둘을 동시에 해서?
Why? Because she can both sing
and play guitar at the same time?
That's all I'm looking for
from these people.
다들 그렇게 맘에
들어하는 것 같은데
Look at you, all jealous.
질투하는 거야?
Come on, Pheebs. You two have
completely different styles.
그럴 필요 없어
넌 스타일이 완전히 달라
저 가수가 더...
She's more....
You know?
네가 더...
And you're more....
내 곁에 있어주세요
Say you'll stay beside me
지금 봤지?
노래 끝나니까 좋아하잖아
See? Everybody else is
happy she's done.
다음 곡의 제목은
'피비, 할 말이 없어
Okay, my next song's called:
"Phoebe Buffay, What Can I Say?
I Loved When We Were...
듀엣이었을 때가 그리워
널 그렇게 떠난 걸 후회해'
...Singing Partners and I Shouldn't
Have Left You That Way."
제목이 길어서
아주 은유적이군
One of those "look for
the hidden meaning" songs.
The One With Phoebe's Ex-Partner
피비
Hey, Phoebe.
Hey, Leslie.
레슬리
How'd you know I'd be here?
날 어떻게 찾았어?
생선 파는 가게에서
블래드를 만났는데
I saw Vlad at the place
where they sell the big fish.
He said you played here a lot, so....
네가 여기서 연주한다고
들었어
I have to go to the bathroom.
나 지금 화장실 갈 건데
If "big-fish place"
comes up again...
생선 파는 가게 얘기가
또 나오면
... I'd like to know if that's several
big fish or just one big fish.
큰 생선 가게인지
작은 가게인지 잘 들어봐
광고음악 한다고 들었어요
So Phoebe says you write jingles.
Actually, I said she abandoned me
to write jingles.
광고음악 때문에 날 버렸다고
할 수 있지
우리가 알만한 거 있어요?
Anything we might've heard of?
네...
Home is never far away
'고향은 멀지 않아요'
Home is Homestar Stew.
'고향의 맛, 홈스타 스튜'
그런데 이젠 안 해요
싫증났어요
But I don't do that anymore.
I got kind of sick of it.
And then I couldn't come up with
anything good, so they fired me.
히트작이 안 나오니까
해고시키더군요
Bummer.
핑계야!
Well, you know, I was just....
있잖아... 난...
I was just thinking
and just hoping that...
내가 바라는 건...
... maybe you'd want
to get back together?
우리가 다시 합치는 거야
싫어, 고맙다
No, but, thanks.
Come on, Phoebe.
Would you just think about it?
생각이라도 해볼래?
알았어
No, but, thanks.
싫어, 고맙다
그래... 또 보자
See you, Pheebs.
되게 냉정하네
That was kind of brutal.
Let this be a lesson to all of you.
너희들도 잘 봐둬
난 한번 배신당하면
'아이스우먼'이 돼
Once you betray me,
I become like the lce Woman.
아주 차갑고, 무지 무지
딱딱한 얼음!
I'm just very cold, hard, unyielding.
You know, nothing can
penetrate this icy exterior.
무엇으로도 절대로 뚫을 수
없는 얼음!
Can I have a tissue?
휴지 좀 줄래?
Is someone in there?
안에 사람 있나?
아뇨
인내력 테스트 중이에요
I'm playing a daredevil game...
'터져서 죽기 전 최후의
순간까지 기다리기'라는 거죠
...called "Wait Until the Last Moment
Before I Burst and Die."
Jeez, man! Did you fall?
이봐요! 빠져죽은 줄...
안녕?
Hi!
지금 시원하시죠?
So did you?
Did you fall high?
여자 화장실이 꽉 차서
여길 이용했죠
Someone was in the ladies' room.
I couldn't wait.
변기 뚜껑은 올려놨어요
I left the lid up for you, though.
You know what, Gunther?
Go ahead.
아저씨, 먼저 들어가세요
저는 이분과...
I'm talking to....
This is where you say your name.
이름 좀 알려 줄래요?
'진저'요
Ginger.
'진저'!
대화 중이에요
Ginger.
I'm talking to Ginger, so...
Don't you have to use the bathroom?
- 화장실 급하지 않아요?
- 아뇨
여기서 얘기나 합시다
No, I just
I'd rather talk to you.
Yes, I do.
사실 급해요
Yes, I do have to go to the bathroom.
이젠 정말 급박해졌어요
There's someone in here.
사람 있소
-Where's Chandler?
-He can't make it.
- 챈들러 어딨어?
- 할 일이 있대
다시 회사 가서 일을...
He said he had to go back
to his job and
어라!
Joey?
조이?
조이 트리비아니?
Joey Tribbiani?
I can see you, okay?
조이, 다 봤어
You're hiding behind the coats.
코트 뒤에 숨었지?
Close one.
친구야
Hi.
안녕
- 어서 와, 자기
- 안녕
Hi, sweetie.
Hello.
Hey, Ross.
안녕하세요?
네
-I've got some bad news.
-What?
- 나쁜 소식이야
- 뭔데?
얼른 식사만 하고
다시 사무실로 와야돼
I can eat,
but I have to come back here.
또? 지난 2주간 매일
늦게까지 일했잖아
Come on. You've worked late
every night for two weeks.
-What is it now?
-It's my fault. I quit today.
이번엔 또 뭔데?
저 때문이에요
오늘 그만두죠
But work comes first!
그래, 일이 우선이지
But that's sad about you, though.
What happened?
어쨌든 안 됐어요
무슨 일이죠? 왜요?
What happened? Burn out?
Burn all out, did you?
지겨워졌나요?
해고됐나요?
He's leaving for a better job.
더 나은 직장으로 옮기는 거야
잘 됐군요, 그럼 오늘이
마지막이죠? 잘 가요!
That's great.
So I guess this is goodbye then.
Goodbye.
Okay, then.
- 그럼, 이만
- 네
- 많이 보고 싶을 거야
- 나도
Well, we're gonna
miss you around here.
Yeah, me too.
-So see you on Saturday.
-Yeah, you bet!
- 그럼 토요일 날 만나
- 그래
Now, you know those
are a delicacy in lndia.
그건 냉정한 태도가 아냐
레슬리가 다시 듀엣하자고
호출한 거야
That was Leslie calling
to see if we can get back together.
It's like the 20th time today.
Yeah, good luck, Leslie.
오늘만 12번째야
잘해봐, 레슬리
아주 큰 상처를 줬나봐?
She must've hurt you bad.
Well, yeah.
You know, we were best friends...
응, 우린 어릴 적 친구야
...ever since we were little.
Our moms worked on the barge together.
우리 엄마들이 함께
유람선에서 일했어
You two must've been so cute,
running around on a barge.
둘이 배 위에서
뛰노는 모습이 보인다!
배 위에서는 못 뛰어!
You never run on a barge!
- 안녕
챈들러 여기 있어?
Is Chandler around?
아니, 여자 만나러 갔어
He met some girl at the coffeehouse.
'진저' 뭐라던데
Ginger something.
안돼!
Sure it wasn't something that sounded
liked Ginger? Like "Gingeer"?
정말 '진저' 비슷한
이름이었어?
혹시 '진지어' 아냐?
아니, '진저' 맞아
No, it was Ginger.
I remember because
when he told me, I said:
똑똑히 기억이 난다구
'여배우... '랬거든
The movie star
어제 내가 피했던 그 여자야
Oh, man!
That's the girl I was hiding from.
When she sees he's my roommate,
she'll tell him what I did.
챈들러 친구인걸 알면
내가 한 짓을 말할 거야
What did you do?
한 짓이 뭔데?
싫어, 몰라
Oh, no! I can't....
I can't tell you. It's the
most awful thing I've ever done.
난 말할 수 없어
내 평생토록 그렇게
끔찍한 짓은 없었어
Don't tell us.
그럼 말하지마
We'll wait till Chandler gets home.
It'll be more fun that way.
챈들러가 돌아오면
더 끔찍한 상황을 만들어줄게
알았어
It was, like, four years ago.
4년 전 일이야
Ginger and I had gone out a few times.
Then one weekend...
'진저'와 몇 번의 데이트 후에
주말 여행을 떠났어
...we went to her Dad's cabin...
나, 진저 그리고,
말썽쟁이 개 페퍼
...just me, her and her
annoying little dog, Pepper.
That night I cooked
this really romantic dinner
아주 로맨틱한 저녁 식사를
준비하는데...
You gave her food poisoning!
식중독에 걸렸어?
I wish.
더 심해!
After dinner, me, her and Pepper
fell asleep in front of the fire.
저녁을 먹고, 우리 셋은
벽난로 앞에서 잠이 들었어
I woke up in the middle of the night
and saw the fire was dying out...
한밤중에 깼는데 불이
꺼지고 있어서, 나무를 넣었어
...so I picked up a log
and threw it on.
Or what I thought was a log.
비몽사몽에
나무라고 생각했지
Oh, my God!
You threw Pepper on the fire!
어머!
개를 불에 던졌어?
I wish.
더 심해!
Another thing I probably
should've told you about Ginger...
'진저'에 대해서 미리 말을
안한 게 있는데, 다리가...
...is that she kind of has a...
...artificial leg.
의족이야
Oh, my God!
세상에!
다리를 불에 던져 넣고
어떻게 했는데?
What did you do after
you threw her leg on the fire?
내뺐지!
I ran!
That's the best kiss I've had...
화장실 앞에서 만난 여자지만
키스는 아주 좋네요
...with anybody I met
in a men's room.
Actually, me too.
저두요
웅덩이에 발이 푹 빠졌어요
Foot all in the puddle!
이런!
정말 싫어!
Damn! I hate that!
얼른 신발을 벗어요
-You'll have to get out of those shoes.
-Don't worry.
걱정 말아요
- 그러다 발이 얼어요
- 안 얼어요
No, really.
You're gonna freeze.
No, I'm not.
You're not?
Have you got a bionic foot?
안 얼다니,
마징가 발이에요?
Someday. Maybe.
그것도 좋겠네요
Funny book?
책 재밌어?
그게 아냐
아까 들은 말이 떠올라서 그래
I'm just thinking about
something funny I heard today.
마크가 "토요일 날 만나"
Mark saying,
"I'll see you Saturday."
Yeah, at the lecture.
맞아, 강연회가 있어
지난주에 말했잖아
I told you last week.
You said you didn't mind.
안돼, 안돼
강연회는 안돼...
It's not the lecture I mind.
설마 마크 때문은 아니지?
Please tell me it's not because
I'm going with Mark.
- 실은...
- 맙소사, 로스?
-Well
-Oh, my God!
I'm sorry, but if you're not
working with him anymore...
미안해, 그렇지만...
같이 일하는 것도 아닌데
왜 계속 같이 다녀?
...why do you still hang out?
내 친구니까
Because he's my friend.
여기 친구들 말고,
더 필요해?
But do you really need
another "friend"?
조이랑 챈들러를 끊으면
마크 만나도 돼?
If I stop playing with Joey
and Chandler, can I play with Mark?
Is that funny?
Am I suppose to be laughing?
농담이야?
웃어야 돼?
I don't know. You thought
"See you Saturday" was funny.
자기는 "토요일 날 만나"가
더 웃기다면서?
Mark is in fashion.
마크는 패션계에 있어
난 같은 분야에 친구가 필요해
I like having a friend
I can share this stuff with.
You guys would never
go to a lecture with me.
우리 친구들이 강연회를
같이 가겠어?
난 가고 싶어
I'd love to go with you.
- 정말?
- 그래
Really?
나도 옷 있어, 고를 줄도 알지
너를 위해서라면...
I have clothes.
I even pick them out.
For all you know,
I could be a fashion...
옷장사도 할걸
... monger.
알았어
같이 가면 나도 좋지
I would love for you to go with me.
What?
왜?
What should I wear?
Now I'm all nervous.
뭐 입고 가?
너무 긴장 돼
You know, they say
"A watched pot never beeps."
냄비 째려보면 삐삐가 울려?
레슬리가 2시간 동안
호출을 안 해
It's been a couple hours...
...and she hasn't called.
물론 상관은 없지만
Not that I even care. I don't.
Why don't you just call her?
네가 전화해봐
전화하고 싶지?
You obviously want to.
You think you know me so well.
나를 잘 안다고 생각해?
Well, don't you wanna?
그럼 안돼?
돼
그래, 난 널 알아
So I do know you.
나도 알아
That's what I said.
Well, so?
그래서?
I can't.
전화는 안 해
날 버린 애야
I can't. She dumped me.
그렇게 믿던 친구였는데
어느 날 갑자기
I totally trusted her,
then one day it was like:
잘 있어, 피비 하고는
가버렸어
"Okay, bye, Pheebs."
Gone!
정말 가슴 아픈 건...
You know what the saddest part is?
내 평생 가장 즐거운 추억이
그 애와 함께 놀던 때였어
When we were playing together,
that was...
...the most fun I've ever had
in all my lives.
My favorite shoes, so good to me
I wear them every day
나의 새 구두가 정말 좋았어
매일 신고 다녔지
Down at the heel, holes in the toes
Don't care what people say
앞꿈치에서 뒤꿈치까지
사람들이 뭐라든 난 좋았어
My feet's best friend
Pals to the end
내 발의 영원한 친구
그걸 신으면, 난 예쁜 소녀가 돼
With them, I'm one hot chickie
어느 어두운 밤이었어...
Though late one night
Not much light
- 난...
- 뭔가 끈끈한 걸 밟았어
I stepped in something icky
Sticky shoes, sticky shoes
끈끈한 구두, 끈끈한 구두
자꾸 웃음이 나와
Always make me smile
끈끈한 구두, 끈끈한 구두
다음에는...
Sticky shoes, sticky shoes
Next time I'll...
...avoid the...
발 밑을 조심할 거야
...pile!
We're beginning to see a lot of
layering of sheer fabrics and colors.
투명감을 주는 직물과
색을 보기로 하겠습니다
For instance, a sheer navy blouse
over a pink....
예를 들면, 투명한 남색
블라우스를 분홍색과...
같이 오 니까 좋아
I'm really glad we came.
You're so pretty.
넌 참 예뻐
I love you.
사랑해
야옹아, 넌 냄새가 고약해
대체 뭘 먹고사니?
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
야옹아, 넌 냄새가 고약해
물론 네 잘못은 아니지
It's not your fault
- 정말 멋지 다
- 그래?
That's great!
You know, you could totally sell this.
그걸 팔지 그래?
아주 완벽해...
It'd be perfect for, like,
a kitty-litter campaign.
고양이 광고 말야
A jingle?
광고? 싫어, 싫어
왜? 돈도 벌고 좋잖아
Why not?
You'd make a ton of money.
내가 돈만 생각했다면
벌써 백만장자가 됐을 거야
If I was in this for the money,
I'd be a millionaire by now.
제발 광고 생각 좀 지울래?
You gotta get out of
that jingle-head.
You're right.
You're right. I'm sorry.
네 말이 맞아
미안해
- 괜찮아
- 그래
That's okay.
지금 들려줄 노래는
아주 슬픈 거야
I'm gonna play a song now
that's really, really sad.
It's called "Magician Box Mix-Up."
제목은
'텅 빈 마술사 상자'
특대 팔찌, 특대 귀걸이 등...
Oversized bracelets,
oversized earrings...
...oversizing of accessories,
in general, is very popular now.
장신구 특대품은
현재 대 인기 상품입니다...
- 안녕
Can I borrow this?
My milk's gone bad.
우유 좀 줘
우리 집 건 상했어
I hate that.
상한 우유랑 섞어 마시느니
차라리 내 차를 빌려줄게
I once had a thing of half-and-half.
Stole my car.
So how was your date with Ginger?
아무튼...
'진저'하고 데이트는 어땠어?
Great.
좋았어
아주 좋았어
It was great. She's....
참 좋은 여자야
외모도, 성격도 다 좋아
She's great. Great looks
and personality. Greatness.
Sounds like she's got the...
발끝까지 다 좋구나?
...whole package.
Joey told you about the leg, huh?
조이가 다리 얘기했지?
Oh, God!
It freaked me out.
솔직히 약간 거슬리더라
그러면 안 되지만, 그랬어
It shouldn't, but it did.
맘에 들어
계속 만나고 싶다구
I wanna keep seeing her,
but it's like:
근데 가끔 이러고 싶어
네 다리는 어디간 거니?
"Hey, you know what?
Where's your leg?"
난 정말 비열한 놈이야
난 정말 비열하다구
I'm the smallest person in the world,
aren't l?
Morning.
좋은 아침!
물론, 쟤가 더 비열한 녀석이지
Actually, he's the smallest person
in the world.
다리 태운 얘기 들었지?
Heard about the leg-burning, huh?
It came up.
그래
Listen, I know it's a long shot, but...
사실,
이런 말하면 안 되지만...
... by any chance,
did she find that funny?
본인도 재미있어 하지?
So I nodded off a little!
그래, 깜빡 졸았어
"Nodded off"?
Ross, you were snoring!
졸아? 넌 코까지 골았어
My father's boat didn't make
that much noise when it hit rocks!
배가 바위에 부딪혀도
그런 소리는 안 날걸!
Come on! Forty-five minutes....
45분이야! 45분 간, 한 남자가
끈 달린 드레스 얘기만 했어
Forty-five minutes, the man talked
about strappy-backed dresses.
그럼 추운 박물관 강당에서의
4시간은 어때?
Okay, how about four hours
in a freezing museum auditorium...
...Iistening to
Professor "Pitstains" say:
피츠테인 교수가 한다는 말이
"Remember that thing that died
a gazillion years ago?
"여러분! 이것은 수백만 년간
죽어있었습니다"
Well, here's a little bone
we didn't know it had!"
"이제야 발견된 이 작은
뼈를 보세요!"
First of all, it's Professor Pitain.
잘 들어
교수 이름은 피테인이었어
그리고 그 뼈는, 날개가 있지만
날지 못했던 공룡 거였구
And second of all,
that little bone proved that...
...that particular dinosaur had wings
but didn't fly.
그 날 내가 들은 말을
해줄게
Okay, you know what I just heard?
어쩌구, 저쩌구, 어쩌구, 저쩌구!
A hundred million people
went to see a movie about what I do.
내가 하는 일은 수백 만 명이
좋아하는 일이야
I wonder how many people would go see
a movie called Jurassic Parka.
아니라면, 누가 '쥬라기공원'을
보러 갔겠어?
Oh, that is so
- 그건 달라
- 아니지!
A bunch of out-of-control jackets
take over an island!
수많은 옷들이
섬 전체에 널려있었지
If what I do is so lame...
내 일이 하찮게 여겨진다면
굳이 따라올 필요도 없었잖아!
...then why did you insist on coming
with me this morning?
Was it so I just wouldn't
go with Mark?
- 마크와 못 가게 하려고 온 거야?
- 아냐
그저...
너와 함께 있고 싶었어
I wanted to be with you.
I don't know, I feel like lately...
나도 내 맘을 모르겠어
네가 은근히 멀어지는 느낌이야
...you're slipping away from me...
새 직장에 새 동료들...
넌 딴 세상에 있는 거 같아
...with this new job
and all these new people.
And you've got this
whole other life going on.
바보 같은 생각인 건 알지만...
자기와 뭐든지 나누고 싶어
I know it's dumb...
...but I just hate
that I'm not a part of it.
It's not dumb.
자학하지마
But maybe it's okay
that you're not a part of it.
뭐든지 다 나눌 순 없는 거야
내 말 뜻 알지?
You know what I mean?
I mean, it's like...
넌 내 인생의 또 다른
한 부분인 거야
... I like that you're not
involved in that part of my life.
That's a little clearer.
이제 알 것 같아
그런다고 사랑이
멀어지지 않아
See, it doesn't mean
I don't love you...
... because I do.
I love you so much.
왜냐면 자기를 사랑하니까!
얼마나 사랑하는데...
But my work
It's for me, you know?
내 일은... 나만의 거야
나가서 나만의 일을
혼자 하는 거야
I'm out there on my own,
and I'm doing it.
겁도 나지만
나만의 그 일이 좋아
And it's scary,
but I love it because it's mine.
But I mean, is that okay?
- 이제 알겠지?
- 물론이지
Sure.
You're thinking about my leg.
내 다리 생각하죠?
아뇨, 잊어먹고 있는데
왜 그 얘길 꺼내요?
Actually, I forgot.
What's the deal with that again?
Look, it's okay if it bothers you.
신경 쓰이는 건 당연해요
I only need to know
how much it bothers you...
다만, 얼마나 신경이
쓰이는지 알고 싶어요
...because I don't like
wasting my time.
시간 낭비하기 싫거든요
Am I wasting my time?
이게 시간 낭비인가요?
아뇨, 그렇지 않아요
No, I don't think so.
일반적이지 않으니까
빨리 익숙해지세요
It's like anything else.
You just have to get used to it.
What's that?
이게 뭐죠?
That's my "nubbin."
혹이요
What's a nubbin?
무슨 혹이죠?
It's kind of a third-nipple
kind of thing.
그러니까...
세 번째 젖꼭지라고나 할까
You have three nipples?
젖꼭지가 세 개예요?
둘은 일반적인 거고...
Well, you know, two regulars...
...and one that
barely qualifies as a
하나는 가짜라고...
What?
- 왜요?
- 아뇨, 있죠...
Nothing. You know, l....
I just remembered.
I have to leave.
일이 있어서 가야겠어요
You have to leave? Now? How come?
지금... 지금 간다구요?
왜요?
혹이요!
아니, 일이요
Well, it's nubbin.
Nothing!
You know what?
I'll see you later.
그럼...
다음에 만나요
I thought you weren't coming.
오늘 못 온다며?
-Where were you?
-Come here, come here.
- 어디 다녀왔어?
- 들어봐
화 내지 마
Don't get mad, okay?
Don't give me a reason to get mad,
okay?
- 그럼 화나게 하지마
- 알았어
I played Smelly Cat for
my old ad agency. They went nuts!
네 야옹이 노래를 전에 있던
회사에서 불렀는데, 좋대
팔려고 만든 노래가
아니라고 했는데...
I told you I didn't want you
to try and sell it...
...and you just big, fat did it anyway!
그걸 팔아버렸어?
5년 전이라면 함께 노래하고
싶어서 뭐든지 했을 거야
I think, five years ago,
I probably would have done anything...
...to play with you.
But I can do it myself.
If I can't trust you, then forget it.
이젠 혼자서도 할 수 있고
널 믿을 수 없으니까, 없던 걸로 해
안돼, 함께 하고 싶어
I don't wanna forget it.
그럼 네가 선택해
You know what?
You have to choose.
세상에서 가장 중요한 게
고양이 냄새라면
If the most important thing
on the planet to you...
...is this cat-poopy thing,
then you can have Smelly Cat.
가서 그걸 불러
대신 우린 갈라지자
But we won't be partners.
So what's it gonna be?
어쩔래?
야옹아,
넌 냄새가 고약해...
-Smelly cat, smelly cat
-Problem odor in the litter box?
냄새가 납니까?
Don't change your kitty,
change your kitty litter.
고양이를 바꾸지 말고
먹이를 바꾸세요
야옹아, 넌 냄새가 고약해
물론 네 잘못은 아니지
It's not your fault
Sorry, Pheebs.
안 됐다, 피비
그래... 괜찮아?
You okay?
응, 정말 괜찮아
I actually am.
Because, you know, life's gonna
hand you all kinds of stuff.
삶은 우리에게 정말
많은 것을 주는구나
이런 일을 겪으면서
삶의 교훈을 얻잖아
You learn your little lessons
and hopefully you grow.
-You wanna hear a new song?
-We'd love to.
새 노래 들어볼래?
- 응
- 듣고 싶어
광고에 미친 지지배
Jingle bitch screwed me over
Go to hell, jingle whore
지옥에나 가, 지지배야
지옥에나 가, 지옥에 가
Go to hell, go to hell, go to hell
That's all I have so far.
여기까지 만들었어
Well, hello!
내가 오셨다!
-Where you been?
-The doctor.
- 어디 갔었어?
- 병원에
Is everything okay?
- 다 괜찮대?
- 응
Just had me
a little nubbin-ectomy.
꼭지 절제술 받았지
그래!
내 꼭지도 이제 정상이야
Two nipples, no waiting.
Well! Just like Rachel
in high school.
고등학교 때 레이첼 얘기네
뭐?
What?
농담이야
네 개성을 말한 거야
Come on, I was kidding!
It was such an obvious joke.
That was an obvious joke.
그래, 개성이다
난 생각도 못했는데
왜 못했을까?
And I didn't think of it. Why?
The source of all my powers.
내 개성일 수도 있었나?
Oh, dear God, what have I done?
도로 붙여버릴까?